

11541 BLUCHER AVENUE, UNIT 142 GRANADA HILLS, CA (818) 404–6961 CHRISTIANMIKHAEL@YAHOO.COM CHRISTIANMEDRANO.COM

FOCUSES

UX/UI Web Development Branding Print Graphics Motion Graphics

TOOLKIT

Design

Illustrator

Photoshop

InDesign

After Effects

Premiere Pro

Experience Design

InVision

Felix

Development

HTML

CSS

jQuery

PHP

Wordpress

PERSONAL STRENGTHS

Flexibility

Ideation

Analyzation

Leadership

Communication

PASSIONS

Technology

Fitness

Video Games

Film/Entertainment

Music

Photography

LINKEDIN.COM/IN/CHRISTIANMEDRANO BEHANCE.COM/CHRISTIANMEDRANO

OBJECTIVE

My steadfast goal is to maintain a continuous search for innovative solutions, immerse myself in the development of enhanced experiences, and constantly look for creative ways to apply newfound knowledge. As a designer, adaptability and a receptive mind are my strongest and most valuable assets. In my eyes, success is a result of strong work ethic motivated by the pursuit of self satisfaction.

EXPERIENCE

Graphic Design Intern

Universal Music Group (UMG) June 2017 - August 2017



Core Designer

The Center for Visual Communication (VISCOM) January 2017 - Present

Managed projects, lead and cooperated with design teams, corresponded with clients, wrote project proposals and work orders, drafted invoices, and produced creative solutions for on campus clients as well as various local and national businesses.

Student Graphic Artist

University Student Union, CSUN June 2016 - January 2017

Developed print advertisements and collateral such as posters, banners, and giveaway items to promote the various programs and facilities. Assisted with production when necessary.

EDUCATION

B.A. in Arts, Minor in Interactive Marketing

California State University, Northridge (CSUN) Degree in Progress

- University Scholar (2017-2018 Academic Year)
- Member of the Deans List (2014-2015, 2015-2016, 2016-2017 Academic Years)
- President of the Student Advertising Graphics Association (SAGA) (Spring 2017)
- Officer of SAGA (Fall 2016, Fall 2017)
- Member of Beta Gamma Sigma business honors society